It was 2007, and I was Amanda Diva.
I had just come home from the Floetry remix tour
and decided to take a shot at doing my own album.
And I took a poem that I had done on Deaf Poetry Jam.
Please give me one Deaf Poetry welcome to Miss Amanda Diva.
Y'all good?
Good.
All right.
I got 40 MCs on my block,
walking with a bop, claiming that they real hip-hop.
And turned it into this, 40 MCs featuring Q-Tip.
Off my first music album, Life Experience.
Available at amandadivamusic.com.
This is K Slay the Drama King,
chilling with Amanda Diva, 40 MCs.
You already know what it is.
I love this guy.
The heart of these dudes,
coming up to me, oh, I can be.
Suck in bed, I got beats.
I can spit a hot 16.
I'm talking with a bop, claiming that they real hip-hop.
80 feet in Timbs and sagging jeans.
Rhyming about cream, chasing the same dream.
This rhyme is a little dig.
About the 40 MCs on what seems like every block in New York City.
It's a pity most ain't rhyming.
For the love, it's for the fame.
Treating this culture like it's a game.
The mental state is getting minds when they script between the lines.
They ain't worried about the rhyme.
One got shot, one got tough.
It didn't take much for the MCs to get hooked.
Cause everybody wants to be.
Now it's 2026 and I'm reclaiming my timeline.
As Amanda Diva 2.0.
My new album, Truth Translator, drops June 14th.
It's not a movement.
It's movement music.